Hello, little apprentice!
Welcome to Solution The Game!
Here I will teach you some basic English in an interactive way.
Your first mission will be to find, my five small chickens 
that are scattered in this environment. You will be rewarded for it!
Come on!
You managed to find all five animals.
Thank you!
Now is the time to find my buffalo!
Let’s GO.
Thank you!
Now is the time to find my horses!
Let’s GO!
Thank you!
Now is the time to find my little puppies!
Let’s GO!
Thank you!